Juanhui Li

■ lijuanh1@msu.edu | 🐪 https://juanhui28.github.io/ | 🕠 https://github.com/Juanhui28 | 🦞 East Lansing, U.S.

Summary _

A PhD student at Michigan State University, under the supervision of Dr. Jiliang Tang.

Her research interests include graph mining such as link prediction and knowledge graph. She's also interested in integrating language models with graphs.

Education ____

Michigan State University (MSU)

Michigan, U.S.

PhD in Computer Science and Engineering

Sep. 2021 - present

Sun Yat-sen University (SYSU)Master of Computer Science and Technology

Guangdong, China

Master of Computer Science and Technolog

Sep. 2017 - Jun. 2020

Sun Yat-sen University (SYSU)

Guangdong, China

Bachelor of Software Engineering

Sep. 2013 - Jun. 2017

Publications _

- [1] **Juanhui Li**, Harry Shomer, Haitao Mao, and Shenglai Zeng, Yao Ma, Neil Shah, Jiliang Tang, Dawei Yin. "Evaluating Graph Neural Networks for Link Prediction: Current Pitfalls and New Benchmarking", *arXiv* preprint arXiv:2306.10453, 2023
- [2] Juanhui Li, Harry Shomer, Jiayuan Ding, Yiqi Wang, Yao Ma, Neil Shah, Jiliang Tang, Dawei Yin. "Are Message Passing Neural Networks Really Helpful for Knowledge Graph Completion?", The 61st Annual Meeting of the Association for Computational Linguistics (ACL 2023)
- [3] **Juanhui Li**, Yao Ma, Wei Zeng, Suqi Cheng, Jiliang Tang, Shuaiqiang Wang, Dawei Yin. "Graph Enhanced BERT for Query Understanding", *The 46th International ACM SIGIR Conference on Research and Development in Information Retrieval (SIGIR 2023)*
- [4] Harry Shomer, Wei Jin, **Juanhui Li**, and Yao Ma, Jiliang Tang. "Learning Representations for Hyper-Relational Knowledge Graphs". *arXiv* preprint, 2022
- [5] **Juanhui Li**, Yao Ma, Yiqi Wang, Charu Aggarwal, Chang-Dong Wang, Jiliang Tang. "Graph Pooling with Representativeness", 2020 IEEE International Conference on Data Mining (ICDM 2020)

Experience _

2020-2021 **Internship**: Baidu Inc., Beijing, China

2019.10-2019.12 Visiting Student: DSE Lab, East Lansing, U.S.

Teaching Experience _____

Spring 2023 **Teaching Assistant**: CSE 320 Computer Organization and Architecture, Michigan State University Fall 2022 **Teaching Assistant**: CSE 440 Introduction to Artificial Intelligence, Michigan State University

Awards and Volunteer Services _____

• KDD student travel award, 2022

CIKM PC member: 2023ACL PC member: 2023KDD PC member: 2023

TKDE reviewer: 2023KDD student volunteer: 2022

• AAAI SPC: 2022

· CIKM PC member: 2022